if they trample on further In short, they
если дальше попрут Короче они же атом
will capture the atom there before the atom They have 10 km left
захватят там до атом Им 10 км осталось
to Kursk, about
до Курска где-то
20-25 Yes, they won’t
20-25 Да не не
capture it, Sudzhe knows that’s the same They also
захватят знает Судже так само Так же
said
говорили и
that hello
что привет
Salam
Салам
Saim Okay, relax, I’m from Kursk, I’m
Сайм Ладно расслабьтесь я из Курска я
trolling on the flag they are like that  Glory to Ukraine, I
тролю по фла они такие Слава Украине я
undermine them right away. You are from
такой у них подрывает сразу Вы откуда с
what city of
какого города
Yekaterinburg? I just
Екатеринбург мне только что мужики с
came across men from Yekaterinburg, also 35 years old and 53
Екатеринбурга попались тоже 35 лет и 53
years old, what is it that is calm there now, well, in
года что у вас там спокойно сейчас ну в
Kursk itself. Well, how
самом Курске Ну как
calm it is in Kursk, there is no type of their troops, they are
спокойно в Курске нету типа их войск они
20 km from  we are stopped, but there are drones
20 км от нас стоят но есть беспилотники
flying in and air alerts today there
прилетают и тревоги воздушные сегодня
was an air raid alert five times and
пять раз была воздушная тревога и
transport most stops
транспорт самое останавливается
public transport buses and
общественный транспорт автобусы и
Traliki are standing when, well, when there is an alarm yes
Тралики стоят когда ну когда тревога да
yes it can be for 3 hours You understand
да она может 3 часа быть Понимаешь
Maybe all but
Может всю но
be And what are you
быть А вы чем
doing working for you right now
занимаетесь работаем у вас то сейчас
in short, you once had a shroma, I remember this
короче у вас шрома был когда-то этим
And now I’m saying the head of Yekaterinburg was Roizman And how now Kuibyshev is not Kuibyshev, but
А как сейчас Куйбышев не Куйбышев это А
Kuibyshev understood I thought you said the city of
понял Куйбышев Я думал ты говоришь город
Kuibyshev is Samara Kuibyshevo was called I
Куйбышев это Самара Куйбышево называлась
also understood this is the
ещё понял это фамилия
dude’s last name Well, calm down there, nothing to you
чувака ну вас спокойно там до вас ничего
doesn’t reach Yes,
не долетает Да у нас
of course, but what are the Ukrainians
конечно а что там украинцы
trolling
троллят
with specifically choosing Ukraine? Yes, yes, I,
с специально выбрали Украину Да да я
too, like I specially installed a VPN
тоже типа я специально я VPN поставил
like for myself from the Ukrainian They think that I’m
типа себе с украинской Они думают что я
one of them, it’s such a laugh, take it too,
свой это такая ржака возьмите тоже
hang something up, like they’ll first
что-то повесьте типа они будут сначала
think something-  then you are like your own and then you are
думают что-то вы типа свои а потом вы
like this And who
такие А кем
do you work and do your own thing, you
работаете да своим делом занимаемся
can
можно
say, in short, everyone is going to war. As I
сказать короче всем на войну Я так
understand it, everyone who, in short, is not next to In
понимаю всем кто короче не рядом с
short, when Mariupol was liberated from us, the
Короче когда Мариуполь освобождали у нас
Kursk region, the boys were traveling to liberate, they were
Курской области пацаны ехали освобождали
killed, how many now when it is necessary to
полегло сколько теперь когда надо
defend the Kursk region
курскую область защитить
Akhmat  we saw how this Aladin's bast shoes are
Ахмат видели как этот лапти Аладина
burning, we have everything under control, under
горит у нас всё под контролем под
control, we saw no conscripts were thrown in,
контролем видели не не срочников кинули
some find them, some of ours
ря некоторые находят их некоторые наши
find them,
находят их
and
ещ
that I have an acquaintance in short, he
что у меня знакомый короче по срочке там
was there for conscripts, they still can’t find him for 2 weeks,
был его всё ещё 2 недели не могут найти
from the very beginning when there was a breakthrough  was
вот с самого начала когда прорыв был
given how
дало сколько ему
old he was, he was either 19
лет ему то ли 19
or something When the war
на ни Когда война
or something was put on the border, well, yes And
и чтоли на границу поставили ну ж да А
where was this guy they broke through
где этот Был пацан они прорвали
it in Kursk it turns out
это в Курске получается в части в
he served in some unit He only managed to write to his mother in the morning
служил Он утром только маме успел
something like that there  they were
написать то что типа вот там их куда-то
sent somewhere but didn’t write Where and they say
отправили но не написал Куда и говорит
they’re shooting at the Armed Forces and they can’t get in touch
там ти стреляют в ВС е на связ не
Well, that’s what it is and you don’t want to go
Ну да это такое а сами не хотите поехать
help us here Yes, we’ve already
помочь тут нам Да мы уж
served our emergency
отслужили срочку
dacha here Try urgently when there was no war
дачку тут Попробуй срочку когда войны не
at all there was a freebie  we
было вообще халява была у нас на срочке
can also say that we
тоже можно сказать боевые
were in combat when so and how old are you,
были когда так а сколько вам летне
otherwise you’re already older now I think you’re
а то ты это сейчас уже Я дума вы
older I thought you served there 10
постарше думал ты же там служил там 10
years ago, it wasn’t me who served in Sevastopol and
лет назад не я в Севастополе служил а
that they threw you in Belgorod, in short, also
что вас в Белгороде кидали короче тоже
Kato,
Като
not us at all  they were sent urgently to the seas
не нас вообще по срочке в моря
No, but in Belgorod, what
отправляли Не ну а в Белгороде что вы
did you do? They didn’t throw you anywhere, they just
делали Не никуда не кидали так просто на
went to shoot in Belgorod, if you don’t sign a contract, you
ездили Белгороде а не подпишете контракт
won’t go to defend the Kursk region,
не поедете защитить курскую область
fresh Yes,
свежие Да
something for everyone, in short, I’m asking you,
что-то всем всем короче я ва спрашиваю
Yes, everyone fit in Donetsk for Donetsk
Да всем Донецк за Донецк все вписывались
Donetsk Lugansk we will help Yes for the course
Донецк Луганск мы поможем Да за курс
to fit in
вписаться
there yes No why There are people there anyway they will
там да Нет почему Там же есть по-любому
bring How many they are already
привезут народ что привезут Сколько уже
bringing 6 shorter than August they have been bringing for how long
везут 6 короче августа везут уже сколько
18 days where 18 21 days
18 дней где 18 21 день
3 weeks I have already lost count 3
3 недели я уже даже счёта сбился 3
weeks we were first told that  now
недели нам сначала говорили что сейчас
everything drg went there in short now like her they
там всё дрг зашла короче сейчас типа её
went and carried food with their wife
ходили еду носили с женой
in short and most importantly for everyone in Russia in Moscow
короче и главное всем в России Москве
in general for Muscovites this is the most you know
вообще москвичам это вот самый знаешь
how to say it’s offensive Moscow is stupid discos they have
как говори обидно Москва тупо дискотеки
concerts Yes here in short Belgorod Yes And now
них концерты Да тут короче Белгород Да А
they’ve seen us now in general in short
нас сейчас сечас вообще они видел короче
Kursk  They fired from the multiple rocket launchers,
Курск Из рсзо обстреляли
that is, they are already taking pencils out of the Grad.
то есть уже достаёт Из Града
And what do you have there? There is no air defense there. They
карандашами А что у вас там ПВО нету что
all ask, like, Where is
ли знает Вот все спрашивают типа А где
the air defense, or all the air defense in Donbass
ПВО такой либо всё ПВО на Донбасс
was taken there,
забрали туда
or they should have brought mobile phones a long time ago?
либо должны были давно мобильные
I don’t know. 3 weeks of us are
привести Я не знаю 3 недели нас
shorter than the city.
короче города
southwestern side part Yes,
получается юго-западная сторона часть Да
it’s like it’s not a nine-story building, but a
там типа получается не девятиэтажки а
private sector and it’s already covered it’s already
частный сектор и уже накрывала его уже
covered and that you’re in short, like playing a lottery
накрывал и что ты короче как в лотерею
like I don’t know, I personally don’t know that Donbass
типа я не знаю мне лично тот Донбасс Был
In short,
короче
Crimea was needed, it’s still
нужен Крым ещё
so
так ал
hung hung I thought
зависло завис думалось
not not with us  so, like, the Internet doesn’t cut out,
не не у нас так типа не обрывается
like if something rattles, in short, it
интернета Типа если что-то гремит короче
happens that the lights are turned off, like And you have
бывает что свет отключают типа А у вас
Sirens Around the city, at least there are,
Сирены По городу есть хоть есть есть
now they’re already turned on at first, in the first days they
сейчас уже включают сначала первые дни
didn’t turn it on at all, like you know, Well,
вообще не включали все типа знаешь Ну
the authorities, in short, tried to pretend that
власть короче старалась делать вид что
everything was fine And these  They put up a shelter
всё нормально А эти убежище поставили
No, they put two concrete booths in the center of the city,
Нет там поставили в центре города две
the kind at the stops, you know
бетонных будки такие на остановки знаешь
how big they are, you know Sevastopol, they’re
как по размеру знае Севастополе таких
married,
женаты
you’ll also soon be allocating money
у вас тоже скоро деньги будут выделять
Stopudovo to put up So what are you there? You’re
Стопудово ставить Так что ты там Ты же
not going to sit for 2 hours in this, you know,
не будешь сидеть 2 часа в этой понимаешь
hours Money I think  I think in any case,
часа Деги Я думаю я думаю по-любому
well, like they’ll put
ну типа поставят там на остановках там
a couple of these booths there at the bus stops to
пару этих будок чтобы короче
take photos in short. Yes,
пофотографировать Да что
they’ll hit Maxim if they’re too far away,
они Максим попадут если прит далеко
small fragments will fly, well, at least Well, at
будет маленькие осколки полетят нуну уже
least it protects you know, in short,
хоть Хорошо хоть защищает знаешь короче
there’s
есть
like just sitting on a glass
типа сидеть просто на стеклянной
bus stop is not an option with us, in short  This is what the
остановки не вариант у нас короче вот
court saw, in short,
суд короче
they said the first day of Suji and entered the Suji,
нтмм первый день суджи и вошли в суджи
like And after 4 days they
типа А нам через 4 дня аж
told us, yes, there is no glass there.
сказали да там там короче стёкл нет У
We have people who went to Suji,
нас вот есть люди которые суджи выезжали
they show photographs yesterday there
они фотографии показывают вчера же там
or
или
the day before yesterday, our missiles were launched
позавчера наши же ракеты запускали там
Marova is there So they launched a substation somewhere along
Марова Так что они запускали куда-то по
these lines and that the army,
этим по подстанция и что армия это
in short, somewhere in Lvov there will be no light.
короче где-то во Львове не будет света
They launched something like this here in the Kursk region
Они тут в Курской области
from the Crimea. What’s
с Крыма
your mood
запускали такое А у вас как настроение
now, not all the
сейчас не всех
people? No, not with us anymore  For us, at first,
людей Да нет не у нас уже у нас сначала
like, the first months, everything was hurray hurray,
типа первые месяцы было все ура ура
in short, then it was somehow for everyone, here in our
короче потом всем как-то было вот у нас
Kursk region it was generally calm, somewhere
курскую область вообще спокойно где-то
somewhere on the border they were shooting, Kursk was far away from
что-то на границе стреляли Курск далеко
Belgorod, it was nearby, like there they were 20 meters from the
был Белгороду рядом типа там они 20 м от
border oh We somehow  got used to it already, well
границы о Мы как-то привыкли уже ну
Belgorod Belgorod And in general it was now it
Белгород Белгород И вообще было теперь
came to us
пришло
A little there I saw
Немножко там видел
maybe it was shown on television that
может эту показывали по телевидению что
the girl Sudzhe was wounded was
девочка Судже раненая была
evacuated under fire came under fire didn’t
эвакуировались под обстрел попала не не
see did
видел
n’t sweat
не потели
Newly
Ново
understood So Well, if I don’t know if they
понял Так что Ну если я не знаю если
trample on further In short they will
дальше попрут Короче они же атом
capture the atom  there to the atom They are 10 km left
захватят там до атом Им 10 км осталось
to Kursk somewhere 20-25 Yes, they won’t
до Курска где-то 20-25 Да не не
capture you know Sudzha just like that They also
захватят знае суджу так само Так же
said that they Just you’re sitting Ekb
говорили и что те Просто ты сидишь Екб
Yes, they won’t capture if they
Да не не захватят если что они тебе
need anything
надо
Eh, they’re all so smart, there’s a boy in
Эх все такие умные лежит мальчик в
shorts  you won’t
трусиках не вас не
be captured, I’ve cried myself out, I’m afraid,
захватят я сво отплакался отбоялся
I can’t, of course it’s not you, you’re cool
Я не могу это конечно не Вы прикольные
guys, you just know when
пацаны Да просто знаешь когда
you how many there will be somewhere around
ты сколько там там будет где-то
700-800 kilometers, yes, we’re causing you
километров 700-800 Да от нас отку от вас
pain,
боль
wait, it turns out beyond the Ural
Да подожди вы получается за Уральскими
Mountains or to the Ural Mountains  mountains on on the
горами или до Уральских гор на на
Ural Mountains on the Ural Mountains I understood
Уральских горах на Уральских горах понял
Well,
Ну
yes I understood everything I thought Everything I thought you are
да Всё всё понял Я думал Всё я думал вы
closer to the Volga like yes There if
тут ближе к Волге типа да Там если что
there is something closer to Mongolia and the shorter it is here
есть в Монголию ближе да чем короче сюда
Yes it will be easier for us to go to Siberia until there we will
Да нам на Сибирь проще будет до туда
definitely never find anything  in the tag
точно ничего никогда не найдёт в таге
so
так
yes
да
yes to this maybe if mobilization
да к такое может если мобилизацию
is announced then in short they’ll take you
объявят то короче возьмут вас
go And
пойдёте А
what is it that we have reservation I mean reservation
что так у нас бронь В смысле бронь
Well we don’t go into this category What
Ну не проходим мы в эту категорию Что
does
значит
reservation mean Well reservation it means when
бронь Ну бронь это значит когда если
even if mobilization happens if the
даже мобилизация будет если вот прямо
war just starts  then
война начнётся только тогда нас
they’ll take us But this partial mobilization
возьмут А вот это частичная мобилизация
definitely won’t affect us, in short, like you have
нас точно не коснётся короче типа у тебя
some kind of cronyism, your dad has some kind of
какой-то блат у тебя батя какой-то типа
major like
[__] типа
yes, no, why did he
да Да нет почему он тебя
book you? It’s so cool to book the
забронировал бронь Так прикольно бронь
name. Are you really hearing something like this for the first time?  I
название Ты что ты реально впервые
have a reservation,
слышишь такое то что бронь есть
yes,
да да
well, we have half the city like that,
ну у нас полгорода так
Well, what is this, how is this reservation
откосил Ну а что это как это эту бронь
here? I could also have messed up
сдесь Я бы тоже может короче замутил
something shorter. Well, it’s a matter of getting a job, like
что-то Ну это
getting a job at some
типа устроится на какое-нибудь
enterprise like the military;
предприятие типа воен военное понял ВСС
Ekb, wherever you spit, there is a
у нас так у вас Екб там куда не плюнь
military enterprise here in
военное предприятие у нас
Kursk, you will get a job. Now I understand, you are
Курске устроишься Всё теперь понял вы
all cunning military
все хитро военные
enterprises, you will get all your money there.
предприятия вы там будете се бабки
And we should be in Kursk,
получать А мы в Курске должны
and you just
а вы просто короче
turn out to be
получается
Krasava in short, and are you even Russian or not
Красава а Ты вообще русский или не
Russian, and
русский да
Russian is some kind of bearded
русский какой-то бородатый
habit  Yes, they didn’t just grow a beard, they
хабит Да не просто бороду отрастили
liked it, they came to us in large numbers in the Kursk
нравится так их понаехал у нас в Курской
region before, ahma, in short, there was
области до того как э ахма короче там
Dagestan, there was no one breaking through the
Дагестан кого только не было прорыв
border of all these bearded tiktokers, the
границы всех этих бородатых тиктокеров
wind
ветром
blew
сдуло
everything away so And so it was Akhmat Sila Akhmat
все так что А так было Ахмат сила Ахмат
Sila here, in short, they didn’t
сила тут короче не
trade to come what  should I show you a master class,
торговали приехать что ли мастер-класс
which
какой
one? And you, like M, will jump out like this.
да А у тебя Ты как М выскочишь такой
Let me do them all now,
Давай я сейчас их всех
and you’ve actually brought equipment into the
а у вас технику вообще завезли в
city, I’m telling you, there’s like, near
город я тебе говорю там есть типа возле
this Kurchatov plant, like a nuclear
этой курчатовской станции типа атомной
power plant, they’re digging in making trenches, they’ve brought in
окапывают делают окопы завезли
shrews, we call them they’re like  moles
землеройки мы их называем они как кроты
in short, what is it so that there is no in short m
короче что это такое чтоб нету короче м
you should have brought
вам уже давно давным-давно должны были
mobile air defense
мобильные ПВО
somewhere a long time ago Maybe it exists I know
привести где-то Может оно и есть знаю
mobile they are now mostly all in
мобильно они сейчас в основном все в
Crimea Well, yes, but of course Putin doesn’t want to
Крыму Ну да а конечно Путин же не хочет
remove it from Crimea because for  him Crimea
с Крыма снять потому что для него Крым -
is Crimea and
это Крым а
my region
мый обла
you know the arrival in Crimea it’s all written there
знаешь прилёт по Крыму это все пишут там
that’s where they hit Sevastopol and the Arrival in
вот там ударили Севастополь а Прилёт в
Kursk
Курск всем
everyone so yes Well okay let’s good luck
всем так что да Ну ладно что давай удачи
let’s Glory to Ukraine
давайте Слава Украине
guys
пацаны
Well what Russians Dawa
Ну какие русские Дава
Write to my Gra right now the axis of wine  and
Пиши на мий Гра прямо зараз ось вин а
popk tse even more respectfully YouTube occupying
попк це дуже дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through skarg or in your ban and even more
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
richly video I don’t show people immediately I don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams For this purpose,
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
we need to write an operational link in Mali
того щоб ми Мали оперативний звязок
right away and while there in telegra
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
okm video sche tezh tsikava and  korisna
окм видео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we will
информация и мы повинни з вами трима
show you about it YouTube Slava
того чи покаже вам про це YouTube Слава
Ukraine write
украини пиши